Hello hello friends I am Vishal and you are
watching my channel WhatsApp good
t as you can see it is written by Chaar Ghadi
accidentally the first
feature you will see you lover you are also
talking about your interface factory
welcome your tent and blue first model
its reality this is the tarzan video we are going to
make this about the bread as
you can see its font is messed up by default it is
fine from behind but not fine in front
[Music]
this is the Holi ke Dhamaal Kaila the whole thing above that is
chuka this one is
Pitampura
's grace it is completely of Simar so it is
broken boy everything must have broken by hiding
and here the send recharge has disappeared
friends just one side is on turn it on
[Music]
and this one of yours is also broken
you will have to change it here too
and this is the trim
and love will have to check it is correct
if you have to turn off the alarm and this one of yours will be
ginger on the left side so we will make a
video of the fabric process of this saree
which all the things are looking good no  I am wondering
what all we have done,
if you want such information, stay tuned
to your videos and
if you like to watch such videos,
then subscribe to our channel and after
subscribing, turn on the daily notifications
so that you can get notifications whenever MS Word says
that a has happened
[music]
as you can see
we have opened the entire part of the car which was damaged, so let's
see what is the condition of which part,
this is yours,
yes brother, it is okay, right, do
one more part, okay, this is your thing,
it has to be changed,
after that this was not eaten, it is the rear panel,
jhala, that is the
name of the channel
and tell me
what is called inspection, this is called
report, where you put your feet, this is the area,
jhala, jhala, aye
saiya, loot
ajay,
and this is the front channel for the fan to
relax, girl porn 15
phone panel on the phone, it seems the front is fine
but its clip is broken from here, it
seems okay, it has to be set, this is the
center of Arya Inter, this is the complete problem,
which one is this
I covered the left side,
this right side was finished, friend,
okay, your right side is fine, isn't it,
and this friend is a government website, this is also
completely hidden,
I have to change this much respect, the
cart's cart,
as you can see, Meghnad has
opened the
side, I have removed the mud from the old one,
this is your new one, see how it is standing straight,
and this old one is crooked, the house is hidden, it has become the
front, that's why we are
installing the first one, where is your brother,
both the pipes are fine, they are perfectly straight, there is no
problem in five, okay, now
you have to install this, I have to
remove this old one, it is working
perfectly, right, it has not been done, it has been done, it has been done
[Music]
I
just give two
pupils, everything is
fine, the work
here was not working, or the
direction of the A is suspicious,
as you can see, we have installed the plot and
its first set of computers
etc. will be installed, now we are taking care of the handle,
after this we will assemble it, the font side
But both of them and its center, what can you see, all
three are different parts, but we will
first fill the sample for you so that it is
easy to see the stall in the car and it is done quickly, so that
later we and you can see, it is installed here also,
A
Jhaal
[Music]
Dhela, everything, we have cash, A turn it on,
Chief Minister J of
Rajasthan, both of them, do
not have to be installed,
which panels are being assembled, do it
to Ajay, Ajay
and the explanation has been put, this has to be installed, this has to be
installed, A
I need something for your fiber support, this is a
metal item, it is
completely ready, all that was left to do was,
A is done,
install the torch light and indicator cup,
Meghnad is starting, thank you, it is done,
it has a plastic clip, it has to be
installed with caution, it does
not break, if it breaks then it will have to be paid, will it make any
noise, then do it,
yes it is done,
put the alarm,
this is done,
A do it, there was
customer and demand, change both the side panels,
A to
Ajay
[Music]
Do it,
I am sending you
a
WhatsApp message, something has happened
to Ajay, do it
[Music] Do it, it has happened,
I have put it very well, part plus do it, aa aa, hello, how are
you,
a
lady had a
love affair with A.P.J. Thomas Alva Edison, you
can imagine
that a that a
[Music]
Do it,
why is this so, after all, the parents
along with their children should put
a
plate in the well.
MP3
[Music] Do it
and tell it to
all of you, this is Muzaffar Baig,
aa
[Music] Do it
to Ajay, do it
and tell it
to Ajay, something has happened
[Music]
letter aa
[Music] that in
this way, there is a
demand for salt in India,
[Music]
Do it,
you come and give it to me, it has happened, it has happened, it has happened,
hello, hello friends, I am Vishal and you are
watching my channel Workshop Bariatu,
as you can see, the car is completely
ready, this car had an
accidental claim, it has been repaired,
all the parts have been changed, it has been done there.  The
cleaning is complete, this is final, knowing
its rate means how much will it cost,
which company's insurance is from, how much is the total bill,
how much is the cost of which part, it is
time to get it done, okay so let's start
from the front, how much does each item cost,
I am your car, this is the long Singh, okay so
let's start from the top,
now this one from the point, it is called
voucher, the black one, it is called 338,
its price is 338 and this one is called news handle,
which is of blue color, here remember this one
comes assembled for ₹167, there has been a
change on the rally also, there was a little
change, this is a change of ₹10, along with that the
front panel has also changed for ₹
14, ₹100 and this diet has changed,
I have an alarm which goes up for
₹1 and along with that your
calendar has also changed, painter-3 item
changed, I saw all the changes, it was yo yo yo,
this do not eat one was left,
okay but this one was also standing, so this has
changed  Its son-in-law is worth Rs.600 and
both of these are worth Rs.500, so along with that, the obscene has
also changed,
Kunwar is worth Rs.100 and along with this, the
rear one has also changed,
its price is Rs.264
and this one and this one which is called, this one on that
side has changed, the side panel on
which 125 is written, its price is
Rs.1024 and it will be here, so this is your logo set, the
boxer has also changed for Rs.28, 100
and this inner panel of yours has changed, seven
shops, now for Rs.1,
that your plot has changed brother, this has
changed on the lower floor, this is the area and this is
your cyber, see, it was raised here,
not
Vijendra, it is worth Rs.200, 40 and along with this,
your love change website has also changed, it
is a step, ₹70, in
this way the total of the vehicle varies,
20 thousand 9 hundred rupees, let's see, the
bill must have been sent to the company now,
do the
calculation  Look from there, which side panel, I will show from there, the one
here has been changed, this is also
new, the one on the other side is also new, it is okay, so
much stuff has been changed, it seemed there was
not much damage than this, not that
Ramesh Tiwari, the whole extension is of
Tense Future Sudhar Neta
and its for TV has been changed, it has become
too white, we could not repair it, there was confusion in the
purchase and the
alignment of the torch light bill, there is a
cost for that also and in this way the total bill is of
Rs 20009, the bill has just been sent, let us
see in the slot, how much claim is passed, how much
custom has to be paid, I will
write all that in detail in the description box
and you can check with my mother, if you too have
not understood then at last I
want to tell you people that you people should
definitely like the video, do anything in the comment,
like it and share it with your friends,
this will help us in getting our videos, till then stay put
but I am thinking
that I can talk, talk, I can post more on Aaj Tak
channel so that it can get
more growth, it can be our family,
so if you
like the channel and watching such videos  If you are, then
subscribe, definitely subscribe to the channel.
That's all for today in this video, we will
meet in the next video, till then
Jai Hind. You have given a
lot of respect to our video by taking out your precious time and submitting this note
which will give
575 thanks. A
ki a
[Music]
[Music] ki a ki
a
[Music]